

AKIS GAZEPIDIS

DATA SCIENTIST

PROFILE

Data Scientist with experience in information extraction techniques used on do cuments, scraping data through internet and training of machine learning models. My passion is to accelerate internal company processes and lead to data-driven decisions.

CONTACT

2

+30 6986777430



akisgazepidis@gmail.com



LinkedIn Profile



Personal Portfolio



Peristeri, Athens, 12137, Greece



Google Certifications Profile



Microsoft Certifications Profile

HARD SKILLS

- Python
- Snowflake
- Azure Devops
- PostgreSQL
- Azure SQL server
- PowerBi
- Git
- Postman
- Docker
- CI/CD
- MongoDB
- Dbt

EXPERIENCE

DATA ENGINEERING CONSULTANT

D-ONE

Apr 2023- Present

- · Use ETL pipelines to extract, transform, and load data from various sources.
- Build, test and deploy tables into Snowflake database.
- · Query data from Rest APIs and create collections.
- · Provide PowerBi reports through deployment pipelines.

Project: Database Integration project from Azure SQL server databases to one unified Snowflake database.

DATA SCIENTIST

<u>Generali</u>

Jan 2022- Apr 2023

- Integrate Bitbucket version control system in development.
- · Consolidate data with the use of APIs.
- Create RPA bots so as to automate consuming processes.
- Integrate OCR, Machine Vision & Machine Learning fields to RPA bots.

DATA SCIENTIST

Purposeful

Nov 2021 - Dec 2021

- · Collect publication patents through Google's BigQuery.
- Analyze texts with Natural Language Process (NLP).
- · Conduct topic modeling analysis using Latent Dirichlet Allocation. (LDA)

SOFT SKILLS

- Problem Solving
- Critical Thinking
- Adaptability
- Team Working

LANGUAGES

Greek - Native

English - ILTES 6.5

PORTFOLIO

Optimization of Titan's Mill

Deep Learning - loan prediction

Classcentral scraper

Image Handwritting Recognition

NLP - Climate Change IR System

JUNIOR DATA SCIENTIST

Big Blue Data Academy

Apr 2021 - Aug 2021

- · Web scraping with Beautiful Soup, Requests & Selenium.
- Consolidate various data sources using Pandas & JSON.
- · Data visualization using Plotly, Dash, Power BI.
- Recommendation System with Natural Language Process (NLP) & TFIDF

EDUCATION

WORKSHOPS - CERTIFICATIONS

<u>D-ONE</u> - BigQuery Essentials - Nov 2023

Microsoft - Data Analyst Associate - Aug 2023

MASTER OF SCIENCE

<u>American College of Greece</u> - <u>Data Science</u> 2022 - 2024

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE

<u>University of Piraeus</u> - <u>Statistics & Insurance</u> 2011 - 2020

DATA SCIENCE BOOTCAMP 500 HOURS HANDS-ON

Big Blue Data Academy

Sep 2021 - Dec 2021

- Databases (SQL, MongoDB), APIs & Web Scraping
- EDA & Data Cleaning (Pandas, Numpy, Regex)
- Big Data (PySpark) & Cloud Computing (Amazon Web Services)
- Machine Learning (Scikit Learn) & Deep Learning (Keras)
- · Visualization (Matplotlib, Seaborn, Dash, PowerBi)
- · Communication & Presentation skills

DATA SCIENCE ACADEMY 100 HOURS HANDS-ON

Regeneration Academy by TITAN - Code. Hub

Dec 2020 - Jan 2021